<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<channel>

<title>Dockyard News</title>
<link>http://feeds.feedburner.com/DockyardNews</link>
<description>Straight from the source.</description>

<item>
<title>Renovations</title>
<link>http://feeds.feedburner.com/DockyardNews</link>
<description>The site's homepage and other pages have finally been revamped! It's been a short while since this website launched, but it's always refreshing to see an update, and I hope our visitors think the same.</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2016 03:00:00 EST</pubDate>

</item>
<item>
<title>Downloads Coming Soon</title>
<link>http://feeds.feedburner.com/DockyardNews</link>
<description>Sometime soon, the ships will actually start to be released—two years after the beginning of the project in August 2014. With the downloads page coming to a slow completion, ship releases will begin in the near future. The project's progress will continue in the background, and during the time leading up to this, we would like to request your patience.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jun 2016 04:00:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Download Pages Completed!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/downloads.html</link>
<description>The last four pages for the shipping lines in the download section have also been completed today after a short while of more additions and editing! Go check them out!</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 18 Jun 2016 05:00:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Liners 170-172 Added!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/liner-progress.html</link>
<description>Today, three new ships have been added to the progress charts on the Liner Progress page! Check that page out to see which ones they are.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 03:30:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>First Set of Ships Released!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/downloads.html</link>
<description>Today, the first pack of the ships of the project has been released! Visit the Downloads page for more information.</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2016 10:02:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Key News!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/liner-progress.html</link>
<description>Good morning, sailors—for our American ones though, I do hope that you all enjoyed your Independence Day holiday festivities with your friends and families on Monday. Concerning all of us, for those of you who saw Mauretania's status switch from 'ON HOLD' to 'CORRECTING' this morning (or last night), I had made a huge mistake in the conversion process which had otherwise rendered the original model unusable, so I had to completely reconvert the raw SketchUp model of the ship into a usable .x file again so I could continue editing and configuring the necessary components and elements in order for the model to function correctly in Vehicle Simulator. After about an hour's worth of work, I managed to restore relatively everything, and also made a few small previously unnoticed fixes in order to complete the ship. Oh, and if you've all noticed, the first table of ships is completely finished! 19 ships remain (at this point), and from this point on, it won't be long until the first phase of the project is completed! And for those of you wondering when the next set of ships will be released, it will be in the very near future! Happy sailing until then!</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 6 Jul 2016 01:10:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>More Key News!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/liner-progress.html</link>
<description>Good afternoon, sailors. Some changes have been made to the tables displaying the liners, and of course the liner progress tables as well. Entries 108 and 109—originally Caribe and Perla del Pacifico—have been omitted from the tables and replaced with the 1937 version of Nieuw Amsterdam with her original black hull color, being #108 (opposed to the 1956 gray hull version; #40), and #109 being the Mauretania as she appeared in 1928 after Cunard decided to make minor modifications to the ship's interior fittings and superstructure. Perla del Pacifico has been officially cancelled as it would never be completed, and Caribe, the fictional liner belonging to Linea Sudamericana, has moved to the 177th spot on the third Liner Progress table.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2016 13:12:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Ships Released!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/releases.html</link>
<description>Good evening, sailors—the Ward Line ships have finally been released! This pack includes the gorgeous Oriente of 1930, and her ill-fated and infamous sister Morro Castle, also launched in 1930. We hope you enjoy them! Visit the Ward Line page located on the Downloads page to obtain the pack! More ships will be on the way in the near future as well, so happy sailing!</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2016 23:51:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Heads Up</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Hey guys. I apologize for constantly moving the conversion dates one day forward. Fabricio and I have been experiencing some difficulty getting Linea Sudamericana's Chile to export correctly in Deep Exploration, which turned out to be entirely unsuccessful due to the amount of high-resolution PNG images (90 of them; 2 MB each) used on the model, which effectively accumulated the size of the model, and would therefore be inefficient to use in VSF. Currently there are plans to revise the model, but for now, I've had to change the conversion dates twice because of this specific issue, but of course the next (unproblematic) ship's conversion has been rescheduled.</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2016 01:49:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Italian Line Ships Released!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/downloads.html</link>
<description>Good morning, afternoon, evening or night to all of our sailors worldwide! In commemoration of the 60th anniversary of the sinking of the Andrea Doria on July 25-26th, we've decided to release the long-awaited Italian Line ships in a pack containing 13 of the current ships. They can be obtained on the Italian Line shipping line page from the Downloads section. A lot of work went into these particular vessels, so we honestly do hope you all enjoy them too. Happy sailing!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 23:14:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Important News!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/downloads.html</link>
<description>Hello sailors! I finally have another key update for you all today (or tonight), after doing some more work and having a little relaxation time. As you all can see, the first stage—and probably most important stage—of the project is about to come to an end, when the 150th ship is finally completed (after 2 long years), and I will certainly want to celebrate the first important milestone for this point of the project! I know I've been promising another ship pack within the forthcoming days, but I've actually just returned from a small vacation with family, and now I have a little more time before school initiates to manage the project, so I will do just that. On Friday (the 19th), the last of the 150 original ships—being stage 1—will be completed, and I have some plans to put in place before or once that time comes, and that definitely will include some more sets of ships being released. I don't want to keep you all waiting. I do however want to thank of my supporters, friends and collaborators for enduring such a long wait and assisting me with coordinating this project, because I sincerely do appreciate it. As of today, the 149th ship is completed, and it won't be long until the entirety of stage 1 of the project is completed. I apologize for the long delay in updates, but this is why I am providing a much needed one tonight. Until next time, sailors!</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 23:04:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Big Release of Ships!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/downloads.html</link>
<description>Good evening, sailors! The first stage of the project is officially completed as of today; 2 years after the project first began in August 2014! Today the Grace Line, Cosulich Line and Matson Lines' ships have all been released in celebration of the completion of the first stage of the project! They can be obtained on their proprietary pages in the Downloads section of the website, and we really hope you all enjoy them! Until next time—happy sailing!</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 20 Aug 2016 22:34:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Page!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/liner-index.html</link>
<description>Hello, sailors! A new, informational page has been created for this website and the liners that are included in this project. The page's purpose is to serve as an index of images of each ship, as this was previously not available on the website at all. You can get to the page via direct link, the FAQ page, the Contact Us page, and the website homepage. Check out the new index page and see what all of the current ships look like! A new ship pack is also on the way, so stick around to see which one it will be! Thanks guys for your patience, and I wanted to post this as a quick heads up. Happy sailing!</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 5 Sep 2016 19:52:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>10,000 Views!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Hello, sailors! After about eleven long months of website changes, edits, planning and the eventual publishing of the site early this year, we've finally reached 10,000 views from not only our loyal supporters, but from other ship enthusiasts, gamers and other individuals who enjoy and indulge in similar interests as well! I am extremely proud to announce that we are releasing two ship packs to celebrate yet another milestone for our supporters, the project's general success, and our team members themselves as well! I will make an announcement beforehand on the proprietary Facebook groups first, and then this news bulletin should appear on our site (due to its latency) later on after I initially publish it. I definitely do want to thank you all again for supporting this project and the team responsible for it to reach and achieve this exciting accomplishment! It could have never been achievable without you all, and we certainly do cherish everything that we have and done at this point in time reflecting the project, and of course this includes everyone involved in some shape or form of this project! In the meantime, keep watch of the Downloads page on our site to see which ships have been released! There are also more things in store for you all, so please stick around! Smooth sailing for our sailors until then!</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 19:36:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Ship Packs on the Way!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Hey, sailors! I know it's been quite a long time since the last update, but finally I'm proud to say that there is some welcoming news. After a long pause on the development of the ship packs, I'd like to announce that the development is now back in full swing, and today—October 30th—a new one will be released! Later on it will be revealed which one that is, and of course afterwards, it will be freely available for download! This isn't all though! After today's ship pack is released, the frequency of releases is expected to increase dramatically, meaning that immediately afterwards more ship packs will be placed under development and promptly released in a timely manner, as the second stage of the project is winding down to a halt. Before long the third stage will initiate, which mainly concerns the releases of the ship packs and management of other aspects of the project such as remodification and revising the models (possibly for re-release). There's more to come though, so please stay tuned for the further updates! Happy sailing until then!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 10:47:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Ship Pack Released!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Evening, sailors! As promised, tonight the Portuguese ships belonging to the Companhia Colonial de Navegação line have finally been released (after a long pause of ship pack development)! These ships can be found on the proprietary shipping line page in the Downloads section of the site, so please go ahead and enjoy the new release! As also mentioned earlier, there are more ship packs to come as the remainder of the second stage of the project comes to a halt! Please stay tuned, and again—happy sailing!</description>
<pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2016 21:52:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>USL Ship Pack Released!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good evening, sailors! The wonderful American ships belonging to the famous and prestigious United States Lines have been released! Of course these ships include the ill-fated America (1940), and the glamorous United States (1952)! These ships can be found on their respective shipping line page in the Downloads section of the site, so by all means you can go on and try them out for yourselves! Please also place another vote for the possible choices in the poll for the upcoming ship pack on the FAQ page! Stay tuned for further announcements concerning this project! Happy sailing until next time, sailors!</description>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2016 16:38:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Two Milestones!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good morning, afternoon or night to all of our sailors worldwide!! The past two days of this month have been very good ones overall, as the second stage of the project is finally completed—after two long years of planning, development and hard work—and our website has finally reached 20,000 visitors! All 200 ships, stemming from the original set of 150 ships, have finally been completed, and because of this circumstance, the third stage of the project concerning the releases of the various liners can now properly commence without having to interject its progress with conversions of ships, as there are none left to do. This notice is being written because our shipyard is now inactive from this day forward, because there are no more pending ships left to convert which would otherwise have been done in the second stage of the project anyway. Fortunately, this project again gets to begin a new chapter of its progress, and with the beginning of that new chapter being written, we as a team get to begin our own individual chapters as well. Due to the 20,000 visitors being attained for this site, we will celebrate that by awarding you all with a new ship pack hopefully by tomorrow afternoon. With this being stated, starting today the third stage of the project is officially commenced, and the necessary preparations for the upcoming ship releases are also currently being made as well. We however strive to release the ship packs in timely manners with consistency during this stage, as the second stage of the project can no longer be an involvement, but we also have to say that this stage of the project could never have been made possible without our eager supporters, visitors, development team members, and of course Fabricio himself. Again we'd like to genuinely thank you all from the bottom of our hearts for your support and patience thus far with the ongoing progress of the project, and also for your suggestions, comments and participation that has been put forth towards the team for the development of the project itself. For the time being however, we certainly would like for you all to enjoy the releases that are in store for you all within the upcoming days of this month. Thank you all for your time today, and we wish you all happy sailing until next time!</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 3 Dec 2016 00:09:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>About Stage 3</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good afternoon to all sailors worldwide. This is just a small note about the third stage of this project. Since it mainly concerns the releases of the ships, just about every day or other day will a new ship pack be released, as there are no more ships left for conversion at this time. So keep on the lookout for the latest release, which will be listed underneath the slideshow of the homepage, for those who have not noticed. This way, a bulletin won't have to be written each time a ship pack is released. The FAQ page stats concerning the progress of Stage 3 will also be reflected there, as its statistic has recently been included on the page for informative purposes. The ship pack releases will of course be denoted on the Releases page also for informative purposes. The ship packs will attempt to be released alphabetically, although this may actually change sometime soon, but ship packs will still be released. For now however, we would like you for all to sit back, observe, and enjoy our upcoming ship releases. Thank you all for your time, and this will be all for now. Happy sailing to you all, and happy holidays as well.</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 7 Dec 2016 13:54:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>About Ship Updates</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good evening to all sailors worldwide. I wanted to take the time to explain how ship updates will work. When ships are updated in any way, their individual files will be uploaded into the project's cloud storage account and a link will be provided to the individual ship, but the entire pack will also be updated for those who have not yet downloaded it, to include the updated ship in both instances of the file it exists in, and obviously for convenience so no one will have to redownload the entire ship pack for an update to only one (or maybe more) ship(s) within it. We do however hope you have been enjoying our releases over the past few days, and of course there will be many more to come. If you have any questions, please feel free to contact us. This will be all for now; thank you all very much for your time, and happy holidays and sailing to everyone.</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 23:28:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>We've Reached a Milestone!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>A wonderful afternoon to all of our eager supporters and sailors worldwide! Conveniently, after taking a short hiatus of everything related to the project, we've hit yet another milestone today by reaching over 30,000 views for our website a short time after we recommenced progress on the project, and today we want to celebrate the achievement of that milestone by releasing our beautiful selection of French Line ships for everyone to sail that you've all been waiting for, for quite some time now! There are 13 models included in the new French Line pack, and it even includes the lovely 1950 rendition of the Liberté with her winged funnels that was recently added to the selection of ships! We certainly do hope that everyone enjoys this particular pack that we're releasing today due to the amount of time that we spent working on the ships involved, and also because of our supporters like you that were eagerly anticipating the release of this pack of ships. It was aforementioned that we've recommenced work on the project but it is not in full swing at the moment, so please do not expect frequent releases such as the ones within the past few months, as personal matters are being still being tended to and are at the forefront of our concerns at the moment instead of this project, so we certainly do hope you understand this circumstance of ours. For the time being however, we would like for you all to enjoy the ships we are releasing today as an apologetic means of compensation for the time that the project was indefinitely paused without word given for cause. Background work on this project will continue from this point forward and this is all that has to be said for now, so thank you all for your time and support you've given thus far and we will update you all again for any important matters like these. As usual, the releases are found on the Downloads page, and have a happy sailing session! We'll catch you guys later.</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 13 Feb 2017 13:08:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Site Updates/More Ships!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good afternoon, sailors; we do hope you have seen the latest bulletin in the Developers' Words module posted a few days ago explaining the silence we have attributed to for the month of April. Again we do apologize for that and we do intend to be more productive this month in lieu of the circumstances the team members (we) are in. Recently Fabricio and Christopher have been behind the scenes working diligently and continuing development on a new set of ships. The ones that have been currently completed as of now include the beautifully classic Cunarder named Persia, launched in 1855 to assist in furthering and popularizing the transatlantic market, and another classic Cunarder launched in 1861 with the name Scotia. The original and luxurious styling of these mid-Victorian era ships are a true testament to appealing, stylish and decorative British maritime architecture. Surely our supporters and eager sailors can not wait until the actual debut of these ships in the simulator, but we certainly do hope that the liner team does not keep anyone waiting for very long until this point of the project is reached. Chris' Page of this website has also been slightly revamped for those who have not noticed. A new project index page displaying all of his current projects has been rolled out yesterday, and the proprietary information charts have been updated to reflect all of the current information concerning the development statuses of the projects in question, and all of this information is now viewable and accessible on his page to everyone that is interested in seeing what is going on, and some of the new projects that have been started are actually quite interesting themselves, so we advise everyone to spend a period of time viewing his part of this website. This concludes this bulletin and this is all for now though we expect everyone to anticipate more events to come in the near future for the month of May, so please stay tuned. Happy sailing, everyone!</description>
<pubDate>Tue, 2 May 2017 12:16:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Another Milestone/New Release!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>A wonderful morning or afternoon to our sailors today.
To celebrate yesterday's achievement of totaling 40,000+ views on our website but to also reward everyone including our viewers and supporters alike as promised, this morning I'm releasing the humble yet iconic Hamburg-Süd Line ships in our newest package.
(Hot off the press; I hope I didn't make any mistakes).
It includes, among some, Blohm and Voss' historically infamous Wilhelm Gustloff (1937) which was horrifically lost—along with over 10,000 of her fleeing passengers—after being torpedoed in the Baltic during a refugee evacuation/immigration voyage in late January 1945.
Also included among the seven other ships contained in the package is Blohm and Voss' notorious Cap Arcona (1927), which was also catastrophically lost in early May 1945 just prior to the cessation of WWII after Royal Air Force aircraft consecutively bombarded the vessel along with the small freighter Thielbek with bombs and gunfire and having over ~5,000–7,500 concentration camp survivors aboard.
Our project team certainly hopes that the individuals who download our newest ship package do enjoy the ships that are included, and that the ships are sailed by these individuals throughout the virtual seven seas without harm or bother. We also intend for the month of May to be a little more eventful than the previous two months to compensate for the lack of activity for the project in spite of the ongoing matters we have that must be tended to. Regardless, we still intend to work on the project ardently to maintain a decent routine to avoid long periods of inactivity.
The Hamburg-Süd Line shipping line page on the Downloads page contains the link for the newest package of ships to be downloaded since they are now released.
You can also check out the published posters for the releases on the new Poster page in the Releases section of the site at http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/rpsts.html.
I think that this is all I have for now, but I do intend to keep everyone informed and posted on any upcoming events such as releases that involve our project so please stay tuned if you're interested. Our website will also reflect the current information sometime soon. We wish everyone calm seas and happy sailing, and we'll see you guys later.
</description>
<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2017 12:16:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>New Releases!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good evening to all of our sailors worldwide!
Today, after a series of notable updates, we're finally releasing two wonderful add-ons belonging to our project; they are the Shaw, Savill and Albion Line's distinguished Dominion Monarch of 1938, and the Cunard Line's classically stunning Servia of 1881. Our Servia add-on also features functioning sails on the fore and mainmasts along with two functioning helms situated at two viewpoints on the ship.
For those of you who have already downloaded the Cunard Line add-on pack that was previously released, the current one has now been updated to include the Servia (1881). The new Shaw, Savill and Albion Line page that hosts the Dominion Monarch can be found at the bottom of the Downloads page on this site, among the other changes and renovations.
We have several more ships planned to create as well! For the time and effort we are taking to create, convert, and configure these add-ons for our project, these endeavors can certainly be compensated with a small donation that you can make to support the liner project team.
To continue the progress of our project, we are currently accepting all potential donations that are going towards it, our team members, and our endeavors invested into it. We would certainly like to thank those of you who have taken the time already to make a small donation to our project as well! For those of you who are willing now to make a donation, you can visit the Donations page of our website and view all of the clarifications and information that is present there, at http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/donations.html.
This is all we have for now, so please stick around for upcoming releases and information. We do also hope that you guys enjoy the newly released add-ons too, so thank you guys for your time and participation this evening. If there are any issues or potential errors present on the site or within our add-ons, please let us know so they can be corrected.
Happy sailing, everyone!
</description>
<pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2017 22:48:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

<item>
<title>Follow-Up!</title>
<link>http://fabricio3d.weebly.com/</link>
<description>Good afternoon to all of our sailors worldwide.
We're rolling right along. Today (rather yesterday; 8/9), we're releasing the fictional Italian Line sisters Giotto and Palladio, which were aesthetically/architecturally idealized or conceptualized as early or mid-1960s (c. 1960-1965) ocean liners with the intention of luxuriously, swiftly and comfortably traversing the Atlantic in approximately 3¾-4 or less days at a top speed in excess of 30–32 knots.
The sisters can be found within the updated Italian Line package, which can be obtained from the Italian Line page in the Downloads section of our website, and we do certainly hope that our supporters and viewers alike enjoy the new releases today. More project developments and releases are to come hopefully within the next few days, as well.
Thank you all for your time and this will be all for now, and happy sailing to everyone!
</description>
<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2017 12:18:00 EST</pubDate>
</item>

</channel>

</rss>